And we're just going to--
I want to say it's not a limitation,
but it's kind of like just going to our body.
So you can close your eyes, get comfortable,
and we're just going to breathe together.
Not sure what to say.
Yeah, you're just going to-- yeah, if you want,
you can close your eyes, or you can lower your gaze.
Just so that you kind of go back to simplicity,
the present moment, we're listening to the music,
we're inhaling through the nose gently,
exhaling through the mouth for a couple of times,
inhale through the nose, exhaling.
And as we're exhaling, we're letting
go, any pressure from the day, stress to be here on time,
whatever is crowding our mind, we're exhaling it.
And throughout this moment, you're
invited to just breathe in your own rhythm
in a very natural way, but maybe slowing the pace a little bit
and going back to the present moment,
just feeling those sensations.
And so you can feel the flow under your feet,
resting on the ground, gravity is holding you.
So you can surrender, you can actually relax your body,
letting your body weight, relax on the ground, rest.
And start relaxing the shoulders.
And maybe you can even shake a little bit,
so move your shoulders, stretch your neck.
I'm breathing, you can roll the shoulders, move the spine.
So it's like you're waking up for the second time
today, but this time you get to set the tone.
You can decide how you're waking up against.
Stretch and just you can yawn, do a big touch,
taking a bit of space in this room,
this whole room is just false.
So feel free to text space and you can bend over,
like start stretching.
Stretching your body and listen to what your body is craving.
Maybe your body wants stillness and doing nothing.
Maybe your body wants to text space.
And if you want, you can come back to stillness.
We've got your breathing, and we're
going to focus in a while for a minute.
So what I mean by that, is you're
going to ask your body internally,
you're going to ask yourself, like, how are you feeling today?
So you're addressing your body and you're curious about it.
How are you feeling today?
And just be curious, so there's no right or wrong.
The body is not feeling good or bad.
The body's feeling, maybe it's feeling tired,
maybe it's been energized, maybe it's
feeling tense in some parts.
So be curious and have a return moment with your body.
And see what comes up for you, maybe something is coming up.
Some tension is somewhere.
It's there any resistance, maybe you're resisting this.
Maybe you're above, but I don't want you to do this.
That's in self is information.
OK, there is a bit of resistance coming from my mind
or my body.
I'm not trying to change you to just listening.
And whatever is coming up, if anything is coming up,
just be a little bit even more curious about it.
So what does it mean?
What is the body trying to say?
So for instance, there might be some tension in the chest.
It's like, OK, what's under that?
What is what is the body trying to say or to protect?
What is that tension telling me?
There is resistance, maybe you're
like, oh, being distracted, it's hard to be in the moment.
So what is that telling you as well?
Is there something behind that?
Is there an anxiety, innovations?
And we're just accepting.
We're just listening, acknowledging.
We're not trying to change.
We're respecting the body, the mind, the sound.
We're respecting whatever the message is today.
OK, we're going to breathe deeply together.
We're keeping health through the nose.
And you're back to the mouth.
We're going to do that three times, one more time.
Together, we're going to do that one more time together.
One last time, keeping health.
And before we open the eyes and cut back.
I would like you to set an intention for today for yourself.
How do you want to show up today for yourself?
Maybe you want to be just enjoying the moment.
Maybe you want to be learning something new.
Just decide what's important for you, for yourself,
to do what you want to do.
What would make you the greatest day?
And when you're ready, you can come back, open your eyes.
And let's touch one more time.
Together.
I like my toes, I just like to go on the head, so well.
And now you can take your seats.
You can stand on the couch or on the floor if you want.
I want to dance now, I feel a little energized.
I can't see, I'm talking to dancers.
I'm going to seat, I guess, just his go-get receipt
for the next few minutes.
Yeah.
And how is everyone feeling?
Why don't we just quickly go around and just want to see
what we're probably feeling?
Good.
Really good.
Yeah.
Any physical sensation of feeling good?
My body like moves.
I don't know if you know, so I couldn't keep still learning.
I was just like, I've found a lot of logo-ish and, yeah,
so today I'm like, oh, fun energy, dancing.
So, yeah, I feel, yeah, really good, connected to your body.
You know what?
Your body moves.
Okay.
Yeah.
I feel really relaxed.
Okay.
I'm just weird.
I can still feel the belly relax.
I feel like we've just done a really busy journey.
And so, through the content, if you may, we've got the rest of our three stands
.
Yeah.
I feel like we've done that.
Yeah, we've done that.
I was like, let me know.
Let's go this way.
Well, just whilst each of them, we've got both of them right here.
I feel good.
I feel like relaxing to the space a little bit more.
I suppose it can be a bit scary, like, coming in, like, yeah, we're going to
shoot, but
now we're a bit more comfortable than I thought it would.
Yeah.
Happy.
Okay.
And by the way, it doesn't need to be a happy, positive thing, right?
But somebody said, yeah, I'm going to be in the knowing that's fine.
You know, I feel good.
Like, saying, listen to music to feel very relaxed.
I feel like tension is because I'm at a desk a lot, so I feel tension in my
neck and
my spine and stuff, but, yeah, feeling good.
Okay.
Yeah.
I feel a bit really relaxed, sometimes a little bit anxious, but I'm still a
bit anxious for
it.
Yeah.
Less anxious.
So I feel more comfortable.
Okay.
Yeah.
Same.
I'm also going to go relax.
When you're sensitive, check in with your body.
Yeah.
Also, it's getting in my shoulder.
The tension.
I'm just trying to breathe into it and let it go.
Yeah.
But yeah.
I feel like rather than, yeah.
Yeah.
We're addicted.
Okay.
Yeah.
Good.
I do that kind of thing every morning, so I like to set my tension and just
have a few
moments of my sound.
Yeah.
But it's nice to do it with both sides.
Your voice is really lovely to listen to.
Yeah.
That's why you're on it.
I'm very self-conscious with my accent.
Oh, no.
I love you.
So nice to listen.
Yeah.
Okay, good.
And from here, I'm feeling good.
I'm being excited.
I feel like today is an adventure.
So I'm excited.
Yeah.
And that's how I feel.
I feel like today is an adventure.
So I'm excited.
Yeah.
And that's how I feel.
I feel like today is an adventure.
So I'm excited.
Yeah.
That's how I feel.
Like who really you are.
Like, I mean, what do you want to show up to do?
Like, I believe you might be on our show.
I believe you want to show up.
Yeah.
But you can decide, you know, what's the energy?
What's the intention?
So I want us to spend just a few minutes on that, everyone.
And I think, like, I, so I coach on feminine energy in the sense of like being
a creative
being, like really inventing your reality, creating your reality.
And I think it's very needed in this world.
It's a very, still very masculine, you know, very masculine in the world, which
we love men,
no problem.
But we need first woman.
No, I'm trying to know.
I love other people.
It's not a bit of a benefit of society as a whole.
I believe as a woman, if we take a bit more space, we express a bit more who we
are.
We show up as our full self a bit more, I believe the world will benefit as a
whole.
And I think it starts obviously with the individual.
So it's very important, I think that we go back to, okay, like, what's my full
self?
What's my, what is it about me?
Like, what's my energy, what's that I want to bring up in the world?
And the way I do that and the way I want to invite you to do that is through
your senses.
So really through your body, through your sensations.
And so it starts with your sensations and your pleasure and sensations.
And yes, it can be sexual pleasure, but it's a lot more like pleasure, like,
how do you
make sure for yourself that you're actually here for your own pleasure first?
So you really, you know, you do the photoshoot, you're here and it's like, okay
, I can feel
the space, I feel good, I'm giving myself the means to really take it all in.
So I have a responsibility as a woman for myself to speak out and just express
what
is in that, I don't need what I want, because I do think we live in a world
where we have
been sort of, you know, society brings this, it's like, we receive a lot, like,
can you
open here?
If it comes back, I'm just going to say, yes, you're a friend here, like,
feminine energy,
being like, you're receiving and it's almost like, per se, and I, and I guess I
have, it
like, I, I, you know, and even in like, construction, you know, you call, like,
employment, you
call the female part and the male part, the female part is always the negative
part and
the male part.
It's just inside, and yeah, I think that's where like, negative space and like,
yeah,
there's a lot of space in us that, yeah, that's, people just want to feel the
day of
shit.
And there's stigma around being a woman and being really like, embracing that.
So it's, so we're shifting that, you know, we're like, no, I'm a creator, we're
creators,
we create life, like, we actually are creators as women, I don't believe we're
passive, we're
receiving bullshit.
No, I'm like creating my reality.
So it starts, right now it starts like, okay, how do I experience this, you
know, where
that's like, good for me, you know, and it's not selfish.
So it's really, you're like, if you feel good, people around you will feel good
, they will
safe, they will feel safer because you can feel your safe, you know, you can
feel those
and so when somebody's grounded and expressed their needs, you, you like them,
you feel
good with them.
You want to embrace that.
So I want us to do that every day and so we can start even now.
So it's really like, I want you to ask yourself, I will take a minute, you can
close your eyes.
If you want, just go back to again, your body.
And we're going back to that, how is the body feeling right now?
And we're doing almost like a mini scan, you're thinking, okay, how is my head,
my mind, is
it busy, so you're scanning and remember, it's not like, oh, it's good or it's
bad.
It's more like, you want to be specific.
So it's full, it's distracted or it's very present, clear mind.
So doing that with your mind.
And then you're doing that from the body so it's the shoulders, the neck, the
jaw and
the back, the hips, the legs, everywhere, which is, we're curious, we want to
know what
does the body want right now?
How does it need to feel safe, rounded, and sometimes tension, I mean, always,
I guess
tension, are often here, it's a signal, your body is speaking to you, it's
telling you
something.
So if there's tension, we're not trying to change it, we're not trying to
breathe so
that it goes away, we're actually counting space for that pain, that tension to
exist
and be heard and be felt for as long as it needs, and once you have done that
scan, you
also ask your soul, your sound, your mind, your own spirit, how is it?
It's then craving there.
And then you can ask your whole self, like your whole self, your present self,
your magnetic
self, think of your as like a, maybe it's a bowl of energy, a light, you can
visualise
that inside of you, like it is like a colour, with texture, and it's like your
magnetism,
your energy, and what colour is it?
The kind of colour is your energy today, the kind of texture is your energy
today, is it
like a little cloud, is it like a liquid, like water, anything?
So you're visualising your energy today, so it's colour, it is a specific colour,
maybe
a texture, maybe even a smell, and you're growing it, as you're thinking it,
you're breathing
it, this bowl of energy, colour, magnetism is growing, growing, growing it, it's
taking
space, it's feeling good, every time you inhale, you're growing that big bubble
of shape around
you, that's your essence, that's what makes you magnetic, you can visualise it
anytime
you want, and then for the last question, all you need to think, when you're
going to
do these photos, when you're going to experience this today, what energy do you
want to bring
with you, what do you want to show up to the world?
It might be highness, playfulness, it might be joy, sparkly, whatever other
energy is,
and the energy you want to share and convey around you today, and we're going
to breathe
together three times again, deep inhale through the nose, and exhale through
the mouth, again
deep inhale, last one, all together, we're sharing energy, deep inhale, deep
exhale,
and then we come back and I think our eyes and kiss each once again, because we
never
touch you now, and now we've done one quick round, and then that's it, what's
the energy
you want to convey today with the word fun, fun, fun, yes, so good, and your
positive
authentic, authentic, attractive, fun as well, fun, it's just love, love, yeah,
that's
something love as well, yeah, yeah, good, for me it's present, just want to be
cheeky,
yeah, amazing, thanks everyone, thanks a lot, thank you very much, I was told
that I am
so I have no idea how long to find, yeah, the therapist is just taking, oh my
God, it's
just to figure out the lines and stuff, okay, so thank you so much, thank you
so much for
that, thanks for being with me, so we've had a piece of money with you, now we
're going
to scale to the gap, all the fill up, yeah, so downstairs we'll get some work,
so it goes
with angles, a glass of psycho, or there's some non-alcoholic stuff, so we'll
have a little
thing, do you want to go first, right, so each person will have two 10 minutes
starts, so
we'll sort of manage the time, tell you who's going next, sort of thing, okay,
I mean I'll
come to you in a moment and see like where roughly you want to go, just come
and shake
20 minutes or you want to be comfortable, as always like, just use the space,
step out
if you want, just grab me or Georgia, if you want anything at all, I am
therapist, I'm
a registered therapist, so if you want anything, I'd like to do anything,
Georgia's very experienced
model, so she can help you with that side of things too, this must be good, so
whatever,
just think about what rooms you want to shoot in, have a look around if you
haven't already
and what outfit you want in each room, so just have a think about that, so we
'll start
with you coming, yeah, so if you want to get ready, just think about what rooms
, so we'll
tell Grace to set up the room you want first, is there any room we cannot go,
or? There's
only, yeah, there's one, it's one, so I sat on it on the front door, I think,
over the
top, over everything else, everything else, we can go, you know what I mean,
yeah, it's
the bathroom. They call for the door, it's cute. They send it in the car to
choose just
the coldest thing. That's a bit cute. Oh, that's cool. I don't know how to hold
that.
It was the middle of the room. It was like all outside. It was like your home
was in and
then it was like, yeah, straight down the stairs. It's all the bed to the room.
It's like you're
going to take smiles, yeah. Yeah, it's good. So now, whatever you want to shoot
, say, it's
completely up to you. You can be like, you know, do you want to be like, do you
want to be
one? So, yeah, so we'll start with clove. You want to get ready close. If we
just leave
our stuff in the room that we came in to start with for now, we'll get dressed
and stuff in there.
And then when anybody wants to use it, we'll figure it out. We'll do it on the
left side
because they'll take a few steps. Yeah, definitely on the left side and we'll
keep that ready for it.
Yeah, I might include a kitchen. I want a little spoon. I want a little spoon.
This is my spoon
of her. So, that'll be it. But I'm like, I don't know. She wants to thump in
once. I don't know. I'm like, I'm coming back. She's like, what? It's not like,
I'm not like, but most of those.